When you stand by each other, you can get through anything.
Encounter is a mystery, thriller, drama film directed by Michael Pearce.
A decorated Marine goes on a rescue mission to save his
two young sons from an unhuman threat.
As their journey takes them in increasingly dangerous directions,
the boys will need to leave their childhoods behind.
Malik Khan, played by Riz Ahmed.
Hattie Hayes, played by Octavia Spencer.
Jay Khan, played by Lucian-River Chauhan.
Shepard West, played by Rory Cochrane.
Bobby Khan, played by Aditya Geddada.
Piya, played by Janina Gavankar.
Encounter (stylized as ENCOUИTƎЯ) is a 2021 crime drama thriller film, directed
by Michael Pearce from a screenplay by Pearce and Joe Barton.
The film stars Riz Ahmed, Octavia Spencer, Janina Gavankar, Rory
Cochrane, Lucian-River Chauhan, and Aditya Geddada.
Encounter had its world premiere at the 48th Telluride Film Festival on September 3, 2021, and was released in a limited
release on December 3, 2021, by Amazon Studios prior to streaming on Prime Video on December 10, 2021.
The film explores themes of alien, alien abduction, alien invasion.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.